carat.com 2015-11-01

# Privacy and Cookie Policy | Carat Global

This privacy policy explains how Carat, a trading division within the Dentsu Aegis Network Group (referred to as "we" and "us" in this policy) may collect and use personal information from you when you use our website ( **www.carat.com** ).

As a business, we are committed to respecting and protecting the privacy of all individuals with whom we interact. We will process your personal information at all times in accordance with applicable privacy and data protection laws.

**Personal information we collect on this website**

We collect information about you if you make use of any of the interactive features within our website that rely on a personalised response, or where you ask us to respond to a query you have, or add your details to one of our alert services. The information we collect is limited to the details we need to provide the specific service you have asked for. We do not collect sensitive information, such as your political or religious beliefs, ethnic background, sexual preference, health or any other sensitive information.

**How we use this information**

Except where required by law, we only use the personal information you provide to us to deliver the specific information or service you have requested. For example, if you have requested further information on our regulatory news, or wish to subscribe to our alert service, or submit an enquiry in relation to a job or career opportunities through this site, though we will only use the email address you provide to us to respond to that request. Without your express consent, we will not use your contact details for any other purpose.

**How we store your personal information**

We are committed to ensuring your personal information is kept secure and confidential and not kept for longer than is necessary. From time to time we may ask other members of our group, or third party service providers, to help us manage our information technology systems. Some of these systems may be located in countries overseas. We will only transfer your information to a third party service provider or overseas, where we are satisfied that adequate levels of protection are in place to protect the integrity and security of any information being processed and compliance with applicable privacy and data protection laws.

**How we deploy “cookies”**

Cookies are small packets of information stored by your web browser when you visit certain websites, including our website. Cookies are generally used by websites to improve your user experience by enabling that website to ‘remember’ you, either strictly for the duration of your visit (using a “Session” cookie which is erased when you close your browser) or for repeat visits (using a “Permanent” cookie).

We do not use cookies to store any personally identifiable information about you.

You can learn more about cookies from allaboutcookies.org.

Our site uses the following types of cookies:

Strictly necessary cookies

These cookies are essential in order to enable you to move around the site and use its features.  These are known as “First Party” cookies.  Without these cookies, services like enabling appropriate content based on your type of device cannot be provided.

Performance cookies

These cookies provide information about how visitors use the site so that we can analyse traffic and understand how our visitors use our site. We use cookies issued by a third party, Google Analytics, for this purpose (“Third Party” cookies). Google Analytics uses its own cookie. These cookies don’t collect information that identifies a visitor.  All information these cookies collect is aggregated and therefore anonymous.  It is only used to improve how the site works. You can find out more about Google Analytics cookies here: <https://developers.google.com/analytics/resources/concepts/gaConceptsCookies>. 

You can avoid the use of Google Analytics relating to your use of our site by downloading and installing the Browser Plugin available via this link: <http://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout?hl=en-GB>.

Functionality cookies

These cookies allow our site to remember choices you make (such as your user name, or the region you are in) and provide enhanced, more personal features.  These cookies will also be used to remember changes you have made to text size, fonts and other parts of web pages that you can customise.  They may also be used to provide services you have asked for such as watching a video or commenting on a blog.  The information these cookies collect may be anonymised and they cannot track your browsing activity on other websites.

Social Media Cookies

These cookies are used when you share information using a social media sharing button or “like” button on our sites or you link your account or engage with our content on or through a social networking site such as Facebook, Twitter or Google+.  The social network will record that you have done this.  This information may be linked to targeting/ advertising activities.  

**By using this website you consent to us deploying cookies as described above. If you do not wish to accept cookies from our site, or would like to stop permanent cookies being stored on your computer in the future you can change the settings in your web browser to decline and / or delete cookies.  See the "Help" section on your browser menu for guidance on how to do this. Note that changing cookie settings may affect certain features within this website.** 

**Our responsibility for website links**

This Privacy Policy is limited to the personal information which we collect and use via this website. We do provide links within this site to other websites, including social media sites such as Facebook, Twitter and LinkedIn and sites operated by other brands within the Dentsu Aegis Network Group (e.g. Carat, Vizeum, iProspect, Isobar and Posterscope). If you follow these links, you should use these sites in conjunction with their applicable user and privacy policies as their data practices fall outside the scope of this Privacy Policy. Further, we can have no responsibility for or control over the information collected by any third party website and we cannot be responsible for the protection and privacy of any information which you may provide on such websites.

**Children’s Privacy**

We do not actively seek to collect information about children aged 12 or under, or create interest segments specifically designed for the purpose of targeting children.  If you have any concerns about your child’s privacy in relation to our Services, or if you believe that your child may have entered PII onto out Website, please contact us at privacy@dentsu aegis.com.

**Information Sharing and Disclosure**

We do not sell or rent any personally identifiable information about you to any third party.

We may disclose personally identifiable information in response to legal process, for example in response to a court order or a subpoena, or in response to a law enforcement agency’s request, or where we believe it is necessary to investigate, prevent  or take action regarding illegal activities, and as otherwise required by law. 

Our agents and contractors may have access to personally identifiable information to help carry out the services they are performing for us.

Data Privacy is important to us.  Dentsu Aegis Network Ltd, within the Dentsu Aegis Network Group, has self-certified with the US Department of Commerce’s Safe Harbor Program to address data transfers from the European Economic Area and Switzerland. Under the Safe Harbor framework, Dentsu Aegis Network Ltd complies with the relevant Safe Harbor principles (“Principles”), which you can view at the U.S. Department of Commerce’s Safe Harbor website at [www.export.gov/safeharbor/](http://www.export.gov/safeharbor/).

**Updates**

We may change this policy from time to time by updating this page with amended terms. You should check this page from time to time to ensure that you are aware of any changes.  This policy was last updated on 27 February 2015.

**Contact us if your information or choices change**

If you would like to stop receiving information from us; or your personal preferences change and you do not want us to send you the information requested; or if you have any queries about how we use your personal information, please let us know by contacting us directly:

Legal Department Dentsu Aegis Network Ltd,  
10 Triton Street,  
Regents Place,  
London,  
NW1 3BF,  
United Kingdom.

+44 (0)20 7070 7700  
E-mail: privacy@dentsuaegis.com

#### CARAT.  
Redefining Media.
